Hello, everyone. I am Yang Yi from Shuntian Group, Jiangsu Province.
I am currently working on the 3D digitalization of clothing.
Today, I would like to share with you the concept of 3D clothing tools and clothing design.
As you all know, the digital wave has already swept across various industries,
including our clothing industry.
For example, the CROA 4-core that we used before,
and the AI tools that will appear in the future,
are all part of our digitalization process.
Creating new technologies and using new technologies is inevitable for human progress.
The digital wave of 3D to 2D virtual reality is emerging in various fields.
From the development of design to the end of sales,
the clothing industry is evolving towards 3D digitalization.
The fashion industry is evolving towards 3D digitalization.
Currently, most of the development of our company is based on digitalized tools.
It can reduce the cost of materials and human resources,
and at the same time shorten the period of the release of our products,
and increase the efficiency of the system,
and increase the acceptance rate of our clothing.
Some companies abroad, such as Google and Amazon,
are also actively developing AI designers.
They want to use the fashion trend report,
trend data, image analysis, and so on,
to create an AI designer.
Although currently, these tools and software
may only be of assistance to designers,
I believe that after the global update,
they will make a huge contribution to the fashion industry.
At the same time, we can also use AIGC technology
to match different clothing design styles,
and make individualized predictions,
to help the fashion industry to judge the quality of the products.
For example, the American fashion brand Tommy
recently announced that it will cooperate with IBM
and the New York Fashion Institute,
or FIT,
to use IBM's technology to carry out fashion decoding.
AIGC, as the current new content,
has been widely used in many industries,
including smart offices,
technology education,
automated production,
and smart medicine,
and of course, our clothing industry.
Currently, our company,
AIGC,
has three processes.
One is planning and planning,
the other is design and development,
and product marketing.
In the planning and planning phase,
we may use some big data on the Internet,
or some data on trends,
to carry out trend and trend analysis,
and then lead to some trends,
including color trends,
industry trends,
and design trends,
and so on,
to connect to our development process.
In the development process,
we may use some trends in the planning phase
to carry out design and design,
and then lead to some trends
that we might not have expected.
Finally,
when these trends go online
or are sold on the Internet,
we can use AIGC technology
to produce online videos
or to produce sales content.
These applications
are inseparable from our software tools,
and we can use AIGC technology
to produce online content.
Here, I have compiled some of the software
that we are currently using.
There are some that you are familiar with,
such as MD,
Clo,
Stealth 3D,
ET,
Blender,
and so on.
There are also some that have just become popular,
such as Mid Journey,
Stable Diffusion,
and so on.
There may also be some
that you have not seen before,
or some logos that you have seen less of.
For example,
the spiral one,
Houdini,
3D Max,
and Maya.
In the past few years,
we have been designing clothes
using some traditional design software,
such as AIPS
or Procreate
that is used on the dashboard.
However,
in the past two years,
all of our clothing design software
has undergone a series of revisions.
We may have used
ET,
Fuyi,
and CAD software
to design clothes.
For example,
we have used CCD,
Blender,
3D Max,
or Maya
to design clothing models,
accessories,
and modeling.
We have also used
Pixblend,
AI,
and PS
to design fabrics
and prints.
Finally,
we have used MD,
Clo,
Stealth 3D,
and Blozeville
to design clothes
using 3D clothing design software.
We have also used
3D clothing design software
to design clothes
in a digital format.
In Intel,
we have used
MD,
Clo,
and NGC
and STABL.
Finally,
we have used
3D Max,
Maya,
and other software
for design
for the design
of the entrenment.
We have used
New Journey
and Stable Diffusion
for the design
of the environment.
Finally,
we have also used
CCD,
Blender,
and Holdney
for the들을
for the pattern
of fabric designs.
On the right,
you can see
the project
that we have recently
collaborated with
One of the requirements of this project is to create a thin, airy, and cool design for the sun visor.
When we are modeling, we will choose a relatively thin fabric,
and create a semi-thin effect.
In Maya and 3D Max, we created an ice-cold background,
and at the same time, we added a strong sunlight.
Finally, in Blender and Hudo, we simulated the thinness of the floating fabric,
and completed a series of visual designs.
This is the presentation of the costume digital selling point.
But can our process really have such an effect?
A few days ago, a friend of mine asked me,
after your company uses these digital software,
have you calculated how much cost you can save,
or how much you can speed up your company's efficiency or progress?
So I did a self-reflection.
I compared some of the time we spent developing designs,
as well as the selection rate of our design designs.
After the comparison, I found that if we use the traditional way of thinking to use 3D,
which is to draw an effect picture,
create a 3D version, and then simulate it with Clover,
and sew the costume.
What did we find?
When we didn't use 3D,
maybe it was in 2017 or 2018,
our designer drew a design,
and it might take half a day,
and then he went to the studio to make a 3D version,
and it might take a day to line it up.
After half a day of training,
the designer gave us a sample of the sample,
and then the board was modified.
After the training, the designer confirmed it.
After the confirmation, it might take another two days to line it up,
and finally, the actual sample is completed.
After this process,
it might take a few days,
14 days, or almost half a month,
14 to 15 days.
After we started using 3D software in 2019,
we found that our designer still needed half a day to draw a picture,
and so did the board.
Then we lined it up for a day.
The only change might be here.
We are now using Clover 3D for a special simulation.
It might take from half a day to two hours.
But actually,
the cost of the 3D model and the cost of the sample is similar.
The cost is not too much.
It might take more than two hours,
and then the designer gives an opinion,
and then the board continues to be modified.
After the designer confirmed it,
we still need to line up for another two days to make a sample.
It is clearly digitized.
It is also a one-time modification.
It used to take 14 working days,
but it still needs 13.5 working days to make a sample.
Our efficiency may have improved a little bit,
but the designer's monthly production may also be reduced.
Then our model may also need to be fine-tuned
before it can be put into the promotion work,
as I said earlier.
We have calculated it carefully,
and it seems that there is no change.
Then we designed a process like this.
Let the designer simulate,
not let the designer do it.
Let the designer simulate with a 3D modeling machine.
Our 3D modeling machine may do something more professional,
such as the design of the client or the long-term modeling.
In this way, we can increase the time and efficiency of the 3D modeling machine.
But we found that if we use this process,
the designer's design style time will also be reduced.
This will also cause such a problem.
At the same time,
it may also take more than ten days.
There is no change.
This will greatly reduce our design time or simulation cycle.
Let's assume that there is no intermediate environment.
If the designer does not know how to model,
if he designs a 3D model by himself,
and then the model is modeled according to his 3D model,
and then the designer comes back to simulate it,
and then finally the design is simulated,
then this cycle will be shortened to half.
It is almost from the first cycle to the second cycle.
This way, the model will be simulated.
If the designer knows how to model a 3D model,
for example, a designer who knows how to model a 3D model,
even if he builds a 3D model in Colossal 3D,
or in his familiar 3D software,
even if he spends one or two days to build a 3D model,
he can adjust it to the model he wants.
He only needs to queue for one day and go down to the simulation center.
It may take one to two days or two to three days.
This way, the model can be simulated.
It is a very, very fast process.
After a series of experiments,
because most designers don't know how to model,
we chose to conduct experiments in the first cycle.
Indeed, some designers can produce two to three,
or even three to four samples a week.
At present, the speed is still quite fast.
There is a designer in our company who knows how to model a 3D model.
He may produce a sample for four to five days.
This is a video of us designing a 3D model directly through a digital tool.
I don't know if you can see it.
Mr. Yang just shared that he can't see the video.
Anna, can we see the video?
Yes, we can see it.
Okay.
Now we are doing a simple board operation in this Pro software.
There is a timer below.
Okay.
This is a simple timer that I made two days ago.
It takes about five minutes to make a 3D model.
Then it takes about five minutes to simulate it.
It takes about ten minutes to complete a simple model of modeling that you want.
It includes hardware design, action, and material confirmation.
After that, it takes about ten minutes to complete a 3D model.
This model is relatively simple.
If it is a raincoat, jacket, or shirt, it may take about half an hour to an hour.
This is also based on our designer's understanding of this model.
In this mode, the model and the model will become a secondary product.
When our design draft comes out, you don't need to make additional designs.
Then you can have our model and the board.
This will shorten the period of sample production.
Because in our Pro software, the board can direct the DXF to our ET,
or directly connect our printer to print the board and send it to our sample room.
But at the same time, we also encountered a difficulty.
Many of my friends said,
if I don't know how to make a board, how should I design it?
Because we also know that many designers are not from the class.
They may like this industry, or like clothing, or love to wear it.
Then they start to learn how to design, or move to another field.
Designers from the class or those who graduated from college
will basically understand a little bit of the model.
But their understanding of the model is not deep enough.
So how should they start designing?
Some people think that the design efficiency will be reduced.
I used to think about the design style for a long time.
Now I may spend a lot of energy to make a board.
It takes a long time to build a board from scratch.
Some people also say that they can't let go of it.
They say that they can design in a very natural way.
Now I may have my hands in the software.
I can't do the design fluently like I did with the lines.
So I want to talk about today's topic.
If you want to solve these problems,
you need to understand a logic,
which is to choose from the category to do the design logic.
That is, the design philosophy of the clothing category in the digital age.
Speaking of the category, we can think about a question.
For example, what is the relationship between the suit category and the clothes category?
For example, at the company annual meeting,
everyone is notified to wear a suit.
But if it is the same colleagues,
when they go out to the team building,
they may choose to wear a suit.
Then in our mind,
the category may be related to our scene and application.
In this way, the needs will be categorized.
To extend the idea,
it is to divide the needs into categories.
Because our design purpose is to solve the problem,
to solve the needs.
That is, I found two pictures.
One is the team building scene.
One is the annual meeting scene.
The same group of people may wear different clothes in different scenes.
But in the same category,
we may have different choices in different scenes.
For example, the same is the suit category.
In the wedding scene,
the suit we wear,
the suit the groom wears,
or the suit our guests wear,
the suit our guests wear,
or the suit we wear at the company office during the meeting,
it must be different.
This is the so-called
the division of the needs and the division of the categories.
Starting from the category,
the design criteria is mainly based on the needs of the people.
Satisfy the needs of the specific people
for different clothes in different situations.
These needs include
the needs of beauty,
the needs of professionalism,
the needs of flexibility,
the needs of empathy,
and the needs of comfort.
From the research of the people,
to identify the division of our products,
this is the first step of our design thinking.
This is a case of the analysis of the people.
Because the analysis of the people,
the market analysis,
has a lot of divisions.
Here I just gave a division of the analysis of the people
that is considered from the four aspects of the geographical,
community, and psychological behavior.
After we do the analysis of the people,
we can get a medical life plan.
Maybe some of you may be unfamiliar with this word.
A medical life plan actually means
that you wear clothes every day
or wear clothes for a week.
We can imagine that every morning
when we wake up,
the first thing we think about is
what we are going to wear today.
We open the closet
and start choosing what we are going to wear today.
For example,
if I have an important meeting this morning,
I may choose a shirt
plus a suit.
If I want to go out today
or go hiking,
I may choose a wedding dress.
This is my daily life plan.
For example,
if I go to work from Monday to Friday,
I may choose to wear some formal clothes.
If I go on a trip on Saturday and Sunday,
I may choose to wear some outdoor clothes.
This is my daily life plan.
This is related to our needs in life.
Then we will have some specific,
detailed needs
in order to generate a detailed evaluation.
So,
we will have some specific, detailed needs
in order to generate a detailed evaluation.
Then we will have some specific, detailed needs
For example,
what is my personality?
What is my personality?
Personality,
color,
style,
and taste.
These four aspects will be designed.
Personality is actually
our daily life
as well as
style,
color management,
color ratio,
color scheme,
and so on.
For example,
we have to deal with the proportion of
social,
and commuting
in the workplace.
The proportion of commuting,
fashion,
home,
leisure is 6 to 1 to 1 to 2.
This is just an example
The management of style
might be by one product.
But then we
recorded
the proportion of
clothing technology
by 80%,
fashion
or fashion
clothes
wear
by 20%.
This is
the standard of
clothing
by most of our people.
Our rating management
might be
by different
clothing combinations,
such as
top,
bottom,
top and bottom,
as well as some clothing accessories, and so on.
Finally, in terms of clothing design,
after having the above life plan,
we can design specific designs
for the type of people we have set up.
For example, what kind of pattern is suitable for them?
The pattern is related to the pattern
in the segment category that we listed earlier.
For example, the example I just mentioned,
let's take me as an example.
The type of clothing I like
may be a little more professional,
or a little more casual.
So, my segment category is
to choose from some of the patterns
in the professional and casual styles.
For example, the jacket I'm wearing today,
it's actually a jacket
that is more outdoor.
The pattern that it separates is an outdoor pattern.
As for the craftsmanship,
it's the traditional craftsmanship and new craftsmanship
in the segment category.
In this segment,
the craftsmanship of this windbreaker,
maybe the ordinary craftsmanship,
what we know may be the pressurized craftsmanship,
or its waterproof craftsmanship,
some waterproof craftsmanship of the fabric,
or some of the lacing,
or the sewing of some of the structure of the zipper,
and so on.
Then, we will also find on this dress,
for example, this screed
and its laser engraving screed,
it is a new craftsmanship.
There is a traditional craftsmanship
and a new craftsmanship combined on this dress.
In terms of fabric selection,
it is also a combination of traditional fabric and popular fashion.
Take this dress as an example.
The fabric used in this dress
may be a traditional nylon fabric,
but it is combined with a more popular
cliquette fabric,
and then it is a three-in-one fabric.
In the middle of the fabric it is combined with,
there is actually a layer of super-thin maza fabric,
which is also the latest
waterproof and breathable fabric in 10K 10K.
It is a very different fabric.
So, this dress has a different scenario,
for example, I can wear it in the rainy day,
and then I can wear it in the cold of the mountain,
which provides two new scenarios.
And then I can wear it in the office,
which is a function that I can wear in the office.
Then there is the material.
The material, we define it
as solving some problems,
for example, the molding pad,
it actually solves one problem,
it solves one problem,
the one problem of the sleeve,
The zipper or zipper is the problem of the opening and closing of our clothes.
And the problem of the degree of change of the zipper.
And finally, the color.
The color is mainly related to trends and functional colors.
Most people like to wear black.
In fact, black is also a functional color.
It reflects the needs of some of us who don't like to show off.
Such needs are also our inner needs.
It solves the functions of our inner needs.
This is an example of how outdoor products have become a trend.
For example, Xiao Wang likes outdoor sports.
And when he has free time,
he will visit Dahao and Shenzhen.
The equipment he needs are
the windscreen catcher, the headlamp and the cover.
Our windscreen catcher's category,
let's say there are many kinds of windscreen catchers.
There are those that are pressure-trim,
those that are not pressure-trim,
and there are the three-in-one windscreen catchers.
There are six types of windscreen catchers in our country.
The example we have here
is the three-in-one windscreen catcher.
The recommended product we give is a standard three-in-one windscreen catcher.
It's a three-in-one windbreaker with a braided version.
It requires some flat workmanship,
and it needs to be pressurized,
and it needs to be two-in-one, which means it needs to be removable.
For the fabric, we might choose waterproof,
composite, functional, and functional braided fabric.
As for the accessories, we have chain, magic sticker,
and spring-loaded collar, and so on.
As for the colors, we might use the common colors in men's clothing,
such as turquoise, green, and black and gray.
We might choose a color that is more popular at the moment.
Once we have decided on the category of the accessories
and our one-in-one plan,
our pattern will have a fixed shape.
This solves the problem we mentioned earlier,
which is that our designers may not know how to make a pattern
or don't understand the pattern.
When we make a pattern,
we are aware of the needs of our audience.
The pattern is a secondary product that appears naturally.
For example, the suit.
It is often misunderstood that the design of the suit has no space,
and there is no way to show our design ability.
Or it may be the same from design to design.
The suit.
People usually wear a suit in certain seasons.
They wear it whenever they have time,
but it is a little small in this case.
The suit has many different kinds of patterns.
We have a variety of jacket and coat collection,
which are made from the different patterns of the suit.
For example,
if we use this basic set of a suit,
that is, a suit with a split front and a front slit,
we can make a jacket suit.
like sports suits, T-shirts, and black suits.
In the jacket style, there are also forest jackets,
hunting jackets, advanced jackets,
and Norfolk jackets, and so on.
In sports suits, there are also standard sports suits
and professional sports suits.
So, the design of our suits is actually a very diverse one.
This is what I just showed you.
For example, this is an English version of Tashdor,
a American version of Tashdor, and a French version of Tashdor.
These are the types of suits.
Some of you may not have heard of the special terms for suits.
But if we look at the design,
for example, the hunting jacket,
which has a chest on the left,
a three-dimensional chest jacket,
or a horseback jacket,
you can clearly see the difference between the two designs.
From a man's suit to a woman's suit,
it will gradually evolve into some of the different types of suits
that we are seeing now.
We can divide the standard patterns of suits
into, for example, its collar, a pimpon collar,
and its button, which is probably a button button,
with two buttons on each side.
The bottom is probably a round bottom.
Then there is a pocket on the double-sided line.
Then there is a hand strap on the left chest.
Then there is a three-dimensional buckle.
Then there is a back open and a back open.
These are all the details of our designs.
With the above design details,
we can start from the basic version of our suit
to make changes and design.
We can design while minimizing our own pattern and then modify it.
These modifications may be concentrated in,
for example, the width of the clothes and the basic size.
The jacket below is actually
inspired by a technical jacket.
After the width and size are set,
the shoulder shape of the clothes,
for example, if you want to design a shoulder sleeve or a shoulder sleeve,
or a full-fledged sleeve,
then the seam allowance and the hemline design,
the amount of hemline processing,
including the chest hemline in our women's suit,
and the shoulder hemline in the men's suit,
how should it be processed?
You can do it by adding a collar,
adding a split line,
or, for example, if we make a fleece fabric,
we can do it by pulling it out,
and then we can process the hemline
and the shoulder hemline.
The fourth point is the design of the leader.
The design of the leader actually determines the appearance of the clothes.
This is what I personally think.
Because the leaders in our custom,
for example, the spiritual leader,
the team leader, and so on,
are all very important positions.
That's why we call them leaders.
In the clothes, the design of the collar,
for example,
actually, the hat is also a kind of collar.
The design of the collar, the design of the sleeve,
also determines whether our clothes are good-looking or not.
So, the design of our collar,
for example, the collar of the collar,
the collar of the collar,
or the collar of the collar of the collar,
the design of the collar may involve, for example,
the two-piece sleeve, the suit sleeve,
or the shirt sleeve, this kind of thing.
The fifth point may be some internal structures.
For example, whether we need to have a pocket inside the clothes,
or whether we need to press the collar inside,
or whether we need to design a two-piece suit inside.
These are some considerations and considerations about the internal structure.
The last point is the design of the parts.
The design of the parts includes our decorative parts,
such as the logo logo,
or adding a decorative zipper here.
These actually don't have a big impact on our overall clothing.
It doesn't affect our functions,
it may only affect our appearance.
But the design of the parts also plays a role in the design of the collar.
After completing the above steps,
the 3D model of our one-piece suit has been completed.
When you think about the type of people,
the type of distribution, the life plan,
the characteristics of the pattern, and so on,
you have basically completed this series of designs.
Then you can choose the correct fabric in your fabric warehouse
and make the fabric support.
This is what I have described to you
through the thinking of the type of product.
What type of product should I choose?
What type of people should I choose?
What type of distribution should I choose?
I have to make a series of designs based on these characteristics.
This is just one of the many design trends we have.
For example, we have a trend website.
We may also have a design trend
that has slightly changed from the previous flagships.
However, I think all design trends
have their own technical aspects.
For example, when I was in college,
I learned to design from the style,
from the trend of the style.
It may capture some of the current fashion selling points
and make some extensions.
So, what I have accepted so far
is that the 3D design we use
is actually the most suitable design from the product category.
Okay.
In the end, I would like to talk about the future of 3D fashion designers.
Recently, I have some self-media accounts.
I have learned a lot about 3D fashion.
Many universities have started digital fashion.
They were founded in 2021 or 2022.
They are now facing the problem of graduation and employment.
Many students have added me on WeChat.
They asked me what I would like to see in the future.
They asked me if I would like to work in the fashion industry
or digitalization.
For example, 3D model designers,
or animation artists, special effects artists, etc.
They don't know what they should do.
Some of them asked me if I could find a job in the future.
They were worried about their future.
So, I would like to take this opportunity
to share some of my views on the future of this industry.
Okay.
I have listed three directions.
If we learn how to digitalize fashion,
we may be able to do it in the future.
One is the brand of small and beautiful designers.
The other is the brand of 3-in-1 designers.
They are the only 3-in-1 designers
that can do digitalization and design.
The other is the golden partner of fashion artists.
What I am referring to is
that there are some fashion business owners in the trade companies.
Our designers may work with the business owners
to solve some of the customers' problems.
It is difficult to do some technical solutions for them online.
What are the three directions?
One is the brand of small and beautiful designers.
The other is the brand of big designers.
It may be a big company.
It may not be a state-owned company.
The last one is the trade company.
That is the one we are talking about.
It is a state-owned company.
These three are the three major directions
that we designers are working in.
However, in the future,
the designers of these three companies
may have to go through a small stage and upgrade.
They may also be eliminated.
The future designers may enter this company.
They may be turned around,
but they are not actually turned around.
They will bring a new motivation to the company.
Let me give you an example of a three-in-one designer.
Many of the designers in our company
know how to build 3D models.
However, some of the new designers,
for example, those who have just graduated from university,
or some of the new designers who have come to our company from other companies,
will discover that their own design style,
their choice rate,
or the level of completion after communicating with the designer
is a little bit worse than the designers who are doing 3D modeling
with 3D software.
Let me give you another example.
When some of our clothing businessmen go out
to talk business with our brand,
the brand may often raise some more tricky questions.
Some of our businessmen may call or have a video conference
to ask some designers or technical guides
to give them an online answer.
Some of our designers who know how to do 3D or 3D models
may take a computer with them to meet their clients.
They may solve the problem of 3D models,
the problem of fabric, and the problem of hardware
in a one-on-one way.
Our clients have given us a very high evaluation.
They think our problem-solving process is very efficient
and they can focus on the key points at once.
In comparison,
the other designers who don't know how to do 3D models
may have similar tasks in the future.
For example, they may have to work with the fabric
to organize the space for the fabric
or other similar tasks.
Designers who know how to do 3D models
will be more and more involved in the core of our clients
or the core of our brand.
So I think 3D design is not just about
how to do 3D models,
but it is a new skill.
It is a new skill in the areas
where we have learned from each person before.
Finally, I would like to tell everyone that
digital automation is a big trend in the business world.
For the fashion companies,
the optimization of the future strategy,
the optimization of the flow,
the delivery of products,
the upgrade of customers,
and the innovation of the business model
are all driven by data.
So,
The fashion industry should quickly expand and enhance digital transformation,
and open up new business methods and channels of communication.
Thank you, everyone. I have finished my sharing.